He moved over to right. They played
Caleb over on that side. So now he's
going to play left tackle for us.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> so what's it like your first draft as a
head coach? What's his experience?
>> Well, we were jacked. I mean, to be able
to move back three spots, pick up a
third and a fifth. What a great job by
Andrew and get the player we targeted
the whole time. And uh I mean, we
couldn't be any more excited. and still
have another pick later on tonight.
>> Tyson was still on the board and you
guys made the trade down. So obviously
must have been your guys number one.
>> No, we targeted Spencer
with Spencer being the first tackle off
the board. What was that you thought
separated him from the rest of this
pretty deep tackle class?
>> As I said, his his character was first.
I mean, the way he's wired, I think the
expectations that we'll have for him
won't even match that he has for himself
and his athleticism, his toughness.
When you want to start off the first
year your regime, I mean, when you start
about, you talk about what you want,
character, toughness, athleticism, he
has it all.
>> There's a lot of speculation throughout
the draft process that Spencer might um
move in inside the guarder center just
because of the the arm length. What did
you see on film that alleviates the
concerns about um you know arm length at
that tackle position?
>> Well, I think his athleticism and his
toughness I I just think all of the I
mean
do I think that's a part of it reach arm
length? Of course it is. But there's
other things that that are involved with
other characteristics that go into I
think he'd be an elite guard as well. I
think he'd be elite center. I don't care
where you put him. I think he's going to
be an elite player. Todd, you you know
what George Warhoff wants in his
lineman. Does does Spencer Fano fit it
better than the others?
>> I won't speak to where we had the other
guys at. I'll just say that we were
excited as heck to be able to get
Spencer.
>> Andrew set of tackles and tackles, but
the fact that Spencer played left early
on is that important for you guys to
see.
>> It's part of the equation. Yes.
those teams. I mean, their physicality
is is sort has always been sort of their
calling card. I mean, how much does
that, you know, that that program DNA,
you know, do you see in in in Spencer
and how much was that an attractive, you
know, part of that?
>> A big piece of it. You go all the way
back to Urban Meyer and then coach
Whittingham. I mean, when you get a
player from Utah, I mean, you get a
player that's physical. They're going to
practice physical. They're going to play
physical. their style, their
expectations of their old line. So, uh,
again, we're fired up.
>> Would you still like to get a receiver
pretty high in this back if you can?
>> Sure.
>> And we we we'd like to add there's a
number of areas we'd add to our team.
That being one of them,
>> you guys at all surprised with how the
board fell previous to your guys?
>> I wouldn't say that. Um,
I think it fell pretty close within
reason. Uh, as far as I could tell being
in there with Andrew and his group, it
fell off the board the way it it
appeared to me that it was going to go.
>> Did you Spencer in for a 30 visit?
Because I know that was
>> We did.
>> Everything that I've already said. I
mean, it's it's it's that uh you know, I
mean, I'm
>> have Spencer fan as your left tackle.
Does it affect the movement of any other
positions on your line that we saw the
other day?
>> Not what we saw the other day was really
who we had, you know, with Elton being
out um Titus being a little bit limited
and trying to put all the pieces
together. Ultimately, once the draft is
over um and free agency and we go to
camp, then we'll work on exactly where
everybody's going to fit. That was here
the other day.
Um, you came in and talked a lot of just
about how it all kind of starts on the
offensive line. You mentioned that, I
know, at the combine. Um, with what the
resources you guys spent in free agency
to sort of bolster that group, now your
first pick is as a tackle. Was this kind
of when you came in and took this job,
what you envisioned as you thought about
kind of rebuilding this offense that it
would start with with figuring out that
group?
>> 100%.
>> Good.
>> All right. Thanks, guys.
See?